Guide to the Morris Raphael Cohen Papers 1898-1981
University of Chicago Library
- Series I: Personal and Professional Correspondence, 1899-1946
  - Correspondence, Handler, Milton Handsome, Marius Hanford, Dean A. C. Harap, Louis Harard, Paul Harcourt, Alfred Harding, T. Swann Harnitt, Helen J. Harris, Benjamin R. Harris, Rae B. Harris, Rachel Harris, William T. Harrison, Earl G. Harrison, G.H. (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, Harrower, Blanche Harrower, J. Hartley Hartmann, Jacob W. Harvard University Haskel, Harry Hasselriis, C. H. W. Hausheer, H. Haye, G. Henry Hazlitt, Henry Headley, Reginald Heath, A. E. Heathly, Allan Hecht, Selig Hefelbower, Samuel G. [Heherware?], Gertrude Heim, Leo Heinemann, Fritz H. (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Helfand, Louis Hellersberg, Dr. Hellman, Lillian Hemmeter, John C. Hendel, C. W. Henderson, Gerard C. Henkin, Louis Henle, James Hennock, Frieda B. Henry Holt and Company Hepner, Samuel Herd, Nathan Herrfeld, Karl F. (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, Herrick, Elinore M. Hershfield, Harold Herstein, Lillian Herzsten, Joseph Hewitt, John Edmond Hexter, Maurice B. Heyman, David Hickey, Richard H., Jr. Hicks, Granville Hicks, Knox Hill, Paul A. Hill, Robert E., Inc. Hill, Ruth Hilly, Arthur J. W. Himmelfard, Milton Himwich, A. A. Hirsch, Mark David Hirsch, William (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, Hirschmann, I. A. Hirschmann, Max A. Hirsdansky, Simon Hirshon, Arthur Hitchcock, C. N. Hitchcock, Margaret Hochfelder, Julius Hocking, Agnes (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Hocking, William Ernest Hodes, Charles Hodgson, S. H. [Hoernlé?], C. Winifred [Hoernlé?], R. F. Alfred Hogan, Charles W. [Hohfred?], Wesley N. Holland, Irwin (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Holmes, A. W. Holmes, Jessie H. Holt, Edwin B. Henry Holt Company Holton, Herbert M. Honor, Jennie J. Leo L. Hood, Frazer Hook, Sidney (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Hopwood, Queenan Horan, Martin Horgan, John L. Horne, Charles F. Horne, Herman H. Horowitz, George Horowitz, Murray Howard, D. T. Howard, Edward Howe, M. A. DeWolfe Howland, Charles P. Huebsch, B. W. Hughes, Everett C. Hughes, Helen MacGill Hughes, Percy Huhn, R. Hume, Robert E. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Hunsaker, Herbert C. Hurcourt, B Hurst, Willard Hurwitz, Henry Husm, Isaac Hussakof, Louis Husserl, Edmund Husserl, Gerhart Husted, Wayne Hutchins, Robert (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Hutchinson, Rosa E. Hyde, James W. Hyman, Jerome Hyman, Jennie Kohn Hyman, Joseph C. Hyman, Julius Hyman, Lawrence Hymes, James L. Hyslop, J.H. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Ilicen, Thomas R. Inbau, Fred E. Inman, Samuel G. Ipcar, Adolph Isaacs, Abram L. Isaacs, Edith R. Isenberg, Arnold Israels, Carlos L. Israels, Charles H. (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Jackson, Gardner Jacobs Jacobs, Leo Jacobs, Louis Jacobs, Melville Jacobs, Murray Jacobsen, Kristen S. Jaffe, A. J. Jaffé, Grace M. Jaffe, Philip J. Jaffé, William (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Jaffin, George James, Alice H. James, [Eldon?] R. James, William Janowsky, Oscar I. Jastrow, Joseph Jászi, Oscar Jefferson, Howard B. Jenning, H. S. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, [Jervey?], Hager W. Jewish Frontier Johnson, Ales Johnson, Alvin Johnson, Edwin C. Johnson, F. Ernest Johnson, George (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Johnson, H. M. Johnson, Robert Underwood Johnson, Roswell Jonas, Bob Jonas, P. Jonas, Ralph Selda Jones, A. H. Jones, Adam Leroy Jones, Betty H. Jones, Rufus M. Jones, Wellington D. Jones, W. Tudor Jordan, William K. Joselwitz, Samuel Jung, Leo Jung, Moses Jungclaus, I. H. Jupiter, Moses Jürgens, Dr. (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Kadish, Mortimer R. Kaempffert, Waldemar Kahn, Abraham Kahn, Edward M. Kahn, Joseph Kahn, Leah Kaller, Horace M. Kalven, Harry, Jr. Kamiat, Arnold Kane, Albert B. (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, Kantorowicz, Hermann Kaplan, Benjamin Kappes, Anthony Karbach, Oscar Karelsen, Eph. A. Karelsen, Frank E., Jr. Karpas, Morris Karpinos, Bernard D. Kattsoff, Louis O. Katz, Jacob Katz, Max Katzoff, Louis (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Kaufman, Nathan Kaufman, M. Ralph Kaufman, Samuel B. Kaufmann, Edgar J. Kaufmann, [Frik?] Kaufmann, Herta Kauvar, C. H. Kaye, E. B. Keedy, Edwin R. Keegan, Margaret Kefauver, Grayson N. Keith, Linton J. Kellogg, Arthur D. Kellogg, Paul (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, Kelly, Robert L. Kelson, J. C. Kendall, Henry Kendrick, John W. Kennedy, F. L. Kennedy, Gail Kenyon Review, Editors Keppel, F. D. Kessler, Mordecai Keyser, C. J. Keyserling, Jennie Hyman Kieval, Howard A. Kilpatrick, William H. (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, Kimmelmann, Dellana Kimpel, Ben King, George [Kipling, Rudyard, per WSK] Kirchwey, Freda Kirchwey, George H. Kirschstein, Morris Kisch, Guido Kitching, Edith Kitay, Philip M. Klapper, Paul Klatzkin, Jacob Klee, Hans Klein, Benjamin Klein, David Klein, Joseph J. (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, Kleinman, Seymour Klenze, Camillo von Klepper, Leah Kline, J. R. Knappen, Marshall Knickerbocker Knight, Frank H. Knight, William Knobel, Mr. Knopf, Alfred A. Knopf, Saul (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Knox, Israel Knox, John Koch, Albert R. Kocourek, Albert Koenig, Samuel Kohn, Henry Kohn, [Harris?] Kohn, Robert D. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Kohut, Mrs. Alexander [Konner?], David Kopetzky, Samuel J. Koretz, Mrs. Jessie G. Korzybski, Alfred Kosch, Irving G. Koshland, William A. Kossover, Sarah Kovar, A. Kovarsky, Abraham (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, [Krane?], Dan Defence Committee Kraus, Lester Kretzker, Paul Krikorian, T. H. Kristeller, Paul Oskar Kroner, Richard Kross, Isidor Krusé, Cornelius Krutch, Joseph Wood (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Kuebler, Paul C. Kugelmass, I. Newton Kuhn, Arthur K. Kuhn, Martin A. [Kuhnert?] Kunitz, Stanley J. Kuntz, Charles Kunuitsky, Maurice Kunz, Joseph L. Kushlevitz, Frances Kuvin, L. M. [Kaudil?], J. L. [Kohup?], Robert O. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Ladd-Francis, Christian Laedler, Harry W. de Lagma, Grace A. Laguna, Theodore de Lake, Edna F. Lakey, Howard Thomas Lalanne, Philias de Lamm, Herbert Lamont, Corliss Lamont, Florence Lamont, [Thomas?] Lamprecht, Sterling P. Landis, Benson Y. Landis, James M. Landman, Jacob Henry Landstrom, Norman (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Landy, David L. Langer, Joseph Langer, Susanne K. Lape, Esther Everett Larrabee, Harold A. Laserson, Max M. Lash, Joseph Lasker, Bruno Lasker, Edward Laski, Frida (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Laski, Harold J. (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Laski, Diana M. Lassen, S. B. Latimer, Ira Lattman, J. Laurie, S. S. Laurin, Charles B. Lauter, Herman Lavitt, Julian Lazar, N. Lazaron, Morris S. Lazerowitz, Morris Leach, Henry Goddard Leary, William H. Lebau, Harry Lebow, Laura R. Lee, Algernon Lee, Otis Lee, Ulysses G., Jr. Leff, Jacob H. Leffingwell, William M. Lefkowitch, Minnie Lefkowitz, Abraham Legate, Ray H. LeGras, Alice Mary Lehman, Irving Lehman, Herbert Leibner, Mildred Leidecker, Kurt F. (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Leighton, J. A. Leiser, Joseph Leiserson, William M. Leland, Waldo G. Lentz, Bernard V. Leon, Xavier Leon, P. Leopold, Foreman N. Leopold, W. Lerner, Melvin Letchworth, Ruth A. Leuba, J. H. Levande, Paul Lever, Althea Levin, Harold H. Levine, Murray Levinthal, Cyrus Levitas, Irving Levy, Aaron Levy, T. Aaron Levy, Beryl Harold (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Levy, Felix A. Levy, J. Montefiore Levy, William Theodore Lévy-Bruhl, L. Lewinsohn, Sam Lewinson, Benno Lewinson, Ruth Lewis, Clarence I. Lewis and Marx (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Lewis, Clarence M. Ley, Albert Libman, E. Lieb, Henry Lieberman, Cora Lieberman, Elias Liebers, Rose Liebert, Arthur Lichtig, Ignaz Lillie, Catherine Lindeman, Eduard C. Linahan, Paul H. Linfield, H. S. Linfield, Seymour Linville, Henry R. Lipkowitz, William Lippincott, Harold E. (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, Lippmann, Walter Lipschutz, Paul Lipsky, Louis Lipton, Irving Litlauer, Sebastian B. (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Littauer, Lucius N. Littell, Philip Littell, Robert Little, Marie Litvin (?), A. Liveright, Horace B. Llewellyn, K. N. Loewenberg, L. Lowenstein, Karl Löftler, Prof. Dr. Loft, Jacob Londow, E. J. Longacre, Charles I. Loomis, Sally Lourie, Judge (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, Lovejoy, Alfred O. (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, Loveman, Amy Lovestone, Jay Lovett, Sidney Lowe, Victor Lowe, Victoria Lowenstein, Solomon Lowenthal, Marvin Lowie, Robert H. Lowrie, S. Gail (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, Ludlow, Louis Lurie, H. L. Luria, Sydney Lydenberg, H. M. Lyman, Elizabeth P. Lyman, Eugene W. Lynd, Robert D. Lynn, Joseph Lysley, Louis [L., B.?] (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, MacArthur, Douglas MacClure, Thomas M. Mack, Julian W. The Macmillan Company Mahin, Amy Ruth Malisoff, William M. Malkan, A. J. Mandelbaum, [David?] Mandelbaum, Maurice Manheim, Harold J. Mannheim, Frank Manny, Frank (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Mansfield, Harvey Marceau, LeRoy Marchbin, Andrew Marcus, Mary Marget, Arthur W. Margold, Nathan R. Margolith, Dr. Marguiles, Joe and Mary Marhenke, Paul Mariash, Irving (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Marin, Amador A. Marks, Marcus Maroi, Helen Marsh, H. D. Marshall, Carrington T. Marshall, James Marshall, L. C. Marshall, Lenore G. Marshall, Louis (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Marshall, Rutgers Marshall, Ruth Martens, Emily Martin, [Everett Dean?] Martin, Charles Martin, Herbert Martin, Prestonia M. Marvin, Walker T. Marx, Alexander Masin, Hyman Mason, Gabriel Maulsby, Allen Maxwell, William H. May, Armaund Mayer, Arthur Mayer, Edith (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Mayer, Joseph Mayer, Leo Mayer, Lillie Mayer, [Mammy?] Mayer, Rachel Mayers, Lewis Mayers, May R. McAndrews, Thomas F. McAvoy, Clifford T. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, McCalmont, D. B., Jr. McCarthy, Edmond McClure, M.T. McCormick, Ada MacCracken, H.N. [McCrael?], S. Jerome McDermott, Charles McDonald, James MacDowell, Edward McGovney, D. O. MacGregor, Frank S. MacIver, R. M. McKay, Frank McKeon, Muriel (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, McKeon, Richard P. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Mackintosh, E. B. MacLeish, Archibald McMahon, Marie McNulty, J. J. McWilliams, Carey Mead, Edwin D. Mead, George H. Mead, Nelson P. Mearns, David C. Mears, Eliot G. Meckline, John M. Medbery, Frances Megan, Charles Meiklejohn, Alex (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Meiner, Felix Meister, Morris Mencken, H. L. Mendes, H. Pereira Merriam, Thornton Merrell, Louis J. Merrington, E. N. Merry, G. Merz, Charles Meserole, Darwin Mestler, G. E. Metcalf, Wilmont Metcalf, Henry Methuen, A. Meyer, Agnes Meyer, Dr. (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Meyer, Arthur (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Meyer, Henry J. Meyer, Leonard Meyer, Marion Meyer, Mildred Meyer, Richard Meyerowitz, Arthur Meyers, Harold Meyerson, Emile (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Mezes, Sidney E. Michael, Jerome Michaelis, L. Michaelson, Louis B. Migdal, Lester C. (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, Mikell, William E. Miles, Irene Milgram, Morris Miller, Dickenson Miller, James W. Milliken, Agnes Mills, Frederick C. Mind magazine Mindell, Louis Mirsky, Ada S. Mishkin, Charles (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Moe, Henry A. Mohr, Edward Monroe, Paul Montague, William P. Moore, Jared S. Moore, John B. Moore, Joseph F. Moore, Justin H. Moore, Kathryn Moore, Merritt H. Moore, [Underhill?] (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, Moran, Harold L. More, Louis T. More, Paul E. Mordell, Albert Morgan, Kenneth Morgenstern, Irvin Morgenstern, Julian Morgenthaus, Henry Morley, Frank Morris, Charles W. Morris, Emma A. Morris, Richard Morse, Livingston B. Mortuner, J. H. Moserowitz, Irving Moskowitz, Bella Moskowitz, Henry Mott, Lewis F. (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, Mottsman, Harry Motz, Lloyd Moulds, John Moulton, F. R. Mount, Katruika S. Mount Sinai Hospital Mumford, Edward W. Mumford, Lewis Munsterberg, H. Murison, A. F. Murphy, Arthur Murphy, Gardner Murray, J. Clark Mussey, Henry R. Muzzey, David S. (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, Nagel, Ernest (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Nahum, Stella Nathan, Otto Nathanson, Jerome Naumberg, Bernard Needles, William Neilson, Robert Neilson, William A. Nelles, Mary Nelles, Walter (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Nelson, Everett Nelson, George Nelson, Leonard Neshwiser Young Men's Benevolent Association Neufeld, Maurice Neuman, Gladys R. Neumann, Franz Neumann, Henry (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Neurath, Otto Neus Nevins, Allan Newton, R. Heltzer New York County Lawyers' Association Forum Committee New York Times, Editor New York World Telegram Nicolson, Margaret E. Nicolson, Marjorie H. Nidel, Louis Niebuhr, Reinhold Nitze, William A. Nobis (?), Mildrid D. Norland, C. Norman, Dorothy Nordheim, L. W. North, Joseph Northrop, Christine J. Northrop, Filmer Nussbaum, Arthur (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Ocko, Felix H. Ogburn, William F. Oko, Adolphe S. Oldenburg, Hildegard Oliphant, Herman Oliver, H. Marshall Olsen, E. C. O'Neill Opler, M. E. Openbrym, Milfred Oppenheim, P. Oppenheimer, Monroe Ortlin, Edward Osborne, Thomas M. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Ostrolenk, Bernard Otto, M. C. Overstreet, H. A. Ozanne, Charles (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Paddock, Robert L. Paine, Russell Palmer, Archie M. Palmer, G. H. Panofsky, Erwin Pantaleone, Joseph Pargot, [Jordin?] Park, Thomas Parker, DeWitt Parker, Irving Parsons, Frank Parsons, Talcott Paskin, L. Passin, Herbert Patterson, Edward Patterson, Edwin (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Patterson, F. A. Paulding, J. K. Peabody, George F. Pearl, Raymond Pearson, F. A. Peatman, John G. Pecora, Ferdinand Perlman, Isadore Perlman, Harold Perlman, Selly Perlman, William S. Perry, Charner (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Perry, Ralph B. Petegorsky, David W. Peterson, Houston Phelan, Gerald B. Phelps, Reginald Phi Beta Kappa Pikholtz, Sol Pinson, Koppel (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Piper, R.F. Plotkin, David G. Plotkin, Moses Pohly, Claire Polisuk, Morris Pollak, Louis H. Pollak, Marion Pollak, Walter H. Pollock, Frederick Pollitzer, S. Poluhoff, Nicholas Pomeroy, Velma Pool, Mrs. David de Sola Poor, Charles Love Popo, Jeanne Porter, H.F.J. Porter, Lucius C. Porterfield, Allen W. Paseo, Naura Poses Kaplan Posner, Reuben A. Post, [Emily?] Postal, Bernard Potter, Mrs. Dean L. (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Pound, Roscoe (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Powdermaker, Hortense Powell, Thomas Reed Prager, R.L. Prager, William Prall, David Wight Prashker, Louis Pratt, James B. Price, Herman Price, Miles O. Prince, Benji Pringle, Henry Procter, Thomas H. Propheta, Rev. D. S. Pulansky, Norman Pulling, Arthur C. Punke, H.H. Purdy, Lawson Purvin, Jenni Franklin Putzel, Charles Putzel, Max (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, Quigley, Helen Rabbins, Charles Rabinowitz, Mrs. Aaron Radin, Max Radin, Paul Radway, Laurence Rainich, G. Y. Rallker, Nancy L. Ramsdell, Edward T. Randall, Evelyn Randall, John Herman, Jr. Randall, Mercedes Randall, Stanley Rangell, Meyer Ratcliffe, S. K. Rath, V. Rathborne, Mervyn Ratner, Conrad (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Ratner, Joseph (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, Ratner, Sidney Ratnoff, Nathan Raub, William Rausen, David Ravage, M. E. Ravidowitz, Jacob Raymond, Dora Neill Read, Conyers Read, Martha Redden, Kenneth Redfield, Robert Rees, James Rees, Mina Reeves, Jesse S. Rehinstein, Asher Reichenbach, Dr. Hans Reichenbach, Helen Reichert, Victor E. Reid, James M. Reider, Joseph Reigenstein, Milton Reinemann, Herbert (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, Reines, Ch. W. Reingold, Louis S. Reiser, O. L. Remer, John W. Reppy, Alison Reubens, Edwin Pierce [Reutger?], Hillard Reustle, Frederick (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Revel, Bernard Reyes, Gorgonio D. Reynolds, Frederick Rich, Sidney Richardson, R. G. D. Richman, Julia Riesenfeld, Stefan Riesman, David Rifkind, Simon H. Riis, Edward Riley, Woodbridge Rios, Fernando Del Las Rittenberg, Louis Robbins, Jannette C. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Roberts, Reginald C. Roberts, Donald A. Roberts, J. W. Roberts, Victor J. Roberts, William H. Robesin, A. W. di Robilant, Irene Robinson, Edward A. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Robinson, Frederick (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Robinson, Gerard Tanquary Robinson, Ira E. Robinson, M. Hessin Robison, Charles B. Robison, Sophia M. Rocker, R. Roehner, Edward T. Roelofs, Howard Rogoff, Louis S. Rogres, A.K. Roosevelt, Theodor Root, Elihu Rorstacher, G. Rosen, Eddie Rosen, Joseph Rosenberg, Harry Rosenberg, James N. Rosenblatt, Samuel Rosenfield, Harry Rosenfield, Leonora (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Rosenfield, Hein Jackson Rosenman, Samuel Rosensohn, Dr. Meyer Rosensohn, Samuel Rosensohn, Mrs. Samuel Rosensohn, William Rosenstein, Emily Rosenthal, Albert J. Rosenthal, Erich Rosoff, Raymond Ross, Ralph Gilbert Ross, [W.S.?] Rossell, Eve Rostow, Nelson Rostow, Eugene Roth, Louis (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Rothman, Robert Rouden, Eleanor Royce, Josiah Rubinow, I. M. Rubinow, Sophie Rubinstein, Louis H. Russell, Bertrand Russell, Patricia Rutledge, Wiley Ruutz-Rees, Janet Ryan, George Ryshpan, Sheba (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Saenger, Gerhart Safir, Shelley R. Sainer, Herman L. Sakier, Abraham H. Salant, Louis Salik, Augusta Salkin, Celia Salit, Norman [Salter?], William Salverini, G. Samuel, Maurice Sander, Charlotte Sandrow, Edward Santayana, George Saponescow, J. Saposs, David J. Sarafan, A. A. Sarton, George [Saurel?], Paul (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Savett, Edward N. Savey, [W.?] Saxton, Stanley E. Saymon, Ignatius Sayre, John Nevin Scadron, Jos. Scancarello, Joseph Schachner, Joseph Schadchen Schapiro, J. Salwyn Schapiro Schapiro Schappes, Morris V. Schattman, Milton Elias Schaub, Edward L. Schechter, Harry Scheuer, Sidney H. (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Schiff, Jacob P. Schiffman, Samuel Schilpp, Paul Arthur Schindler, Sidney Schlossberg, Joseph Schmidt, J. Raymond Schmittkind, Henry T. Schmuck, Peter Schnapp, Samuel S. Schneck, M. R. Schneer, A. Henry Schneider, Charles A. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Schneider, Henry G. Schneider, Herbert W. Schneider, Jack Schneider, Seldon Schneiderman, Harry Schnittkind Schoen, Eugene John (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Schoen, Ludwig Israel Schoffman, Samuel Schoolman, A. P. Schrack, Fred Schrecker, Paul Schroeder, John C. Schulman, Samuel Schultz, Henry Schultz, Lillie Schuman, Frederick L. Schuster, M. Lincoln Schwartz, Abraham Schwartz, Benjamin P. Schwartz, Daniel H. Schwartz, Edward L. Schwartz, Leo W. Schwartz, Marguerite S. Schwartz, Mark Schwartz, Sanford Schwartz, Z. Schwimmer, Rosika (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, The Scientific Monthly Scoon, Robert Scott, Arthur P. Scott, Evelyn Scott, James Brown Charles Scribner's Sons Seashore, C. E. Sebeok, Derso See Derso Sebeok See, F. J. Seeger, Raymond J. Seibert, Ormond de F. Seidel, Samuel B. Seldes, Gilbert Seligman, Edwin R. (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Seligson, Harold P. Sellars, Roy Wood Selsam, Howard Seman, Philip L. Semel, Bernard Senior, James K. Senior, Kate Senior, Mary Senior, Rose D. Shana, Paul Shapiro, Harold Roland Shapiro, Isidor F. Shapiro, Jonas J. Shapiro, Hannah Shapiro, Leo Shapiro, Sadie Shapiro, Samuel Shapiro, Yechtiel Shapley, Harlow (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, Sharfman, I. L. Sharp, F. C. Sharp, Samuel Shauer, Melville A. Shaw, Charles Gray Shear, M. J. Shearer, Edna Sheed Ward Inc. Sheffer, Henry M. Sheldon, Wilman H. Shepard, W. J. Shepardson, Francis W. Shepherd, Harold Sheppard, John W. Shepperson, Archibald B. Shientag, Bernard L. Shiffman, Max Shimer, William A. Shipler, Guy Emery (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, Shipley, Joseph T. Shlivek, Max Shluger, Alexander L. Shohan, Abraham Shotwell, J. T. Shoup, Ruth S. Shryock, Richard H. Shulman, Jacob P. Sibbell, Robert Sicher, Dudley F. Siegel, Hal Sigerist, Henry E. Silberberg, Mendel B. Silberman, S. Silver, Abba Hillel Silver, Isidore Silver, Ivan (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, Silverman, Hirsch L. Silverman, Louis L. Silverman, Sol Silverstein, Julius E. Simon, Julius Simons, Daniel G. Simonson, Lee Singer, Edgar Singer, Isidor Sirkin, Fred H. Sirovich, William I. Siskin, Edgar E. Sisson, C. N. Sisson, E. D. Skvirsky, B. E. Slamovitz, David Slesinger, Donald Slochower, Henry (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Slonimsky, Leon Sloss, M. C. Small, Albion W. Smart, Anna O. Smith, Charles Sprague Smith, Emma P. Smith, Franklyn J. Smith, H. B. Smith, Harrison Smith, Lyn Smith, Mildred Price Smith, Norman Kemp Smith, T. V. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, Smith, William T. Smith, Young B. Smolikoff, Harry Smullyan, Arthur Snow, A. J. Snyder, Louis L. Sobel, Louis H. The Socialist Call Solis-Cohen, D. Hays, Jr. Solomon, Jack N. Somertonensis, Marvinus Sommer, Frank H. Southard, E. E. Spaulding, Edward Gleason Spaulding, William E. Spaulding, L. [M.?] Spectorosky, Mr. and Mrs. I. Speare, Elizabeth (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, Speer, Robert K. Spencer, Anna Garland Spencer, Arthur W. Spencer, Nelson S. Speyer, James Spiegelberg, Flora Spiegelberg, Herbert Spielberg, Rose B. Spiro, Grace Springer, E. F. Springer, M. P. Sprogell, Harry E. Stabler, W. Brooke Stanius, G. Stair, Bird (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, Starr, Frederick Stein, Leo Stein, Aline and Clarence Stein, Nadine Steinberg, Milton Steinman, Dr. Stephan, Frederick F. Stern, Bernhard J. Sternfeld, Robert Sternberg, Matthias Sinai Stevens, Robert Stevenson, Catherine Mary Jane Stewart, Margaret M. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Stimson, Colonel Stitt, Edward W., Jr. Stolberg, Benjamin Stollreither Stone, [Franc?] Stone, Harlan F. Stone, N. I. Storey, T. A. Straus, Ida R. Straus, Isidor Straus, Robert K. Straus, Roger W. Strauss, Lewis L. Strauss, William L. Street, Robert G. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, Strong, C. A. Stroock, Alan M. Stroock, Mrs. M. J. Stroock, Sol M. Strunsky, Sheba Stuart, H. W. Studebaker, J. W. Student Council, CCNY Styler, W. E. Sulzberger, Arthur Hays Sulzbergher, Rachel A. The Survey Swabey, Marie C. Sweedler, Nathan Sweeney, Algernon T. Sweet, Irving (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, Swenson, David F. Swift, Arthur L., Jr. Swinburne (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, Taeusch, Carl F. Talbot, Ellen B. Talmadge, Irving de Witt Talmey, Max Tanimura, J. Tarr, Philip H. Tarski, Alfred Tawney, G. A. Taylor, Helen K. Taylor, Louis Taylor, Maurice Tchernowitz, Chaim Tead, Ordway Teegarden, Robert W. (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, Teller, Sidney Ten Boom, [Corrie?] Theosophy magazine, editors Thilly, Frank Thin, James Thomas, Charles C. Thomas, Milton Halsey Thomas, Norman Thomas, Rosemary Thomas, David, Jr. Thompson, C. Mildred Thompson, [D. D.?] Thompson, James S. Thompson, John W. (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, Thompson, Joseph C. Thompson, C. Mildred Thorn, Samuel E. Thorndike, Edward L. Thorner, Daniel Tilles, Ida Tilley, Ethel Times, editors Tinter, B. A. Titchener Tobin, Lenore [Tobring], Francis Tobring, Signe Todes, Milton Tonieri, Mary Emil Tonkonogy, Jeanne Townsend, H. G. Trachtenberg, Rabbi Trager, Frank Trinkaus, Charles E., Jr. Tripp, M. A. (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, Tufts, James H. (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, Tulin, Abraham Tulin, Anna Tunick, Stanley Turner, Frederick J. Turner, John P. Turner, John R. Turner, Joseph C. Turner, Samuel E. Tussey, Moore C. Tuttle, Charles H. (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, Ullman, Harriet Umber, Henry Unger, Edward Union for the Protection of the Human Person Urban, Wilber M. (Box 12, Folder 14)